And let's quickly tell you how to
А давайте швидко розповім як у підписку
choose a subscription and in fact the first rule is very
обрати і насправді перше правило дуже
simple Choose That so that when
просте Обирайте Ту щоб коли будуть
notifications about payment come, they
приходити натикація про оплату Вони вас
don't annoy you, on the contrary, they bring you comfort that
не дратували навпаки приносили втіху про
you are helping the channel develop.
те що Ви допомагаєте каналу розвиватися
Let's go through all four
давайте пройдемося по всім чотирьом
levels. The first level is the coder Malyuk and
рівням перший рівень - це коддер Малюк і
for 35 UAH per month this is already great
за 35 грн в місяць це вже класна
support for the channel, but for 35 UAH per
підтримка для каналу але за 35 грн в
month you join our
місяць ви доєднуйтесь до нашого клубу
closed chat club in Telegram where we
закритого чату в Telegram де ми
discuss various interesting topics. You
обговорюємо різні цікаві теми Також ви
can also influence the next videos
зможете вплинути на наступні відео тому
because I share plans. You can give
що я ділюсь планами Ви можете дати
feedback. We have some internal
фідбек У нас якісь є внутрішнє
surveys and so on. Also, of course,
опитування і так далі також звісно
any comments from sponsors are the
будь-які коментарі від спонсорів це
highest priority. I respond to
максимально пріоритетно я відповідаю на
these comments as quickly as possible or if
Ці коментарі максимально швидко або якщо
not even quickly, then in detail. The
навіть не швидко то тоді вже детально
next level is the architect of bytes.
наступний Рівень - це архітектор байтів
It costs us 200 UAH and this is already more
він у нас 200 грн і це вже більше
support for the channel and here I am already shooting
підтримка для каналу і тут я вже знімаю
exclusive videos, it can be based
ексклюзивні відео це може бути quaнний
on some existing videos.  it could be
по якимсь існуючим відео А це може бути
some webinars I'm planning a couple of webinars and
якісь вебінари я планую пару вебінарів і
it could be some workshops
це може бути можуть бути якісь воркшопи
and here I can even format these questions from the
і тут Я вже можу навіть ці питання від
sponsors of the architect of bytes level
спонсорів рівня архітектор байтів
into separate videos about the ones I
оформлювати в окремі відео про ті які я
mentioned in the video and
згадував відео і більш детально по
go through everything in more detail The next level is the
всьому проходитесь наступний Рівень - це
superpower of the channel it's very similar to the
суперсила каналу це дуже схожий на
previous level and in fact
попередній рівень і насправді
the superpower of the channel it's the most popular
суперсилоканалу це самий популярний
level with the largest number of subscribers at this
рівень найбільшої підписників на цьому
level and in addition to everything that you will get
рівні і крім всього того що ви отримаєте
at the previous levels at this level there is
на попередніх рівнях на цьому рівні ще
additional content - this is an off-topic video and
додатковий контент - це офтоп відео а
usually it's on the side of the topic - this is a video
зазвичай це на стороні теми - це відео
without editing but someone might be interested
без монтажу але комусь може бути цікаво
and there is already one auto video available to
і уже є одне авто відео доступне для
all sponsors as an example I even made it
всіх спонсорів я як приклад зробив його
available to subscribers of the
навіть доступним для підписників
koder level sponsors Malyuk and I also
спонсорів рівня koder Малюк і Також я
plan some life coding sessions how I write
планую якісь лайф-кодінг сесії як я пишу
code Well and my thoughts on this matter Well and the
код Ну і свої думки з цього приводу Ну і
last level is maximum
останній рівень - це максимальна
support - this is straight super support for the
підтримка - це прям супер підтримка
channel Thank you very much to those who already support
каналу Дуже дякую тим хто вже підтримує
the channel at the maximum level it doesn't give so
канал на максимальному рівні це дає не
many bonuses only two additional
так багато бонусів лише два додаткових
bonuses one of them is  if you have a
бонуси один з них це якщо у вас є якась
topic and you want me to make a video on this
тема і ви хочете щоб я зняв відео на це
topic, write to me, I will make it a priority, it is
тему пишете я роблю це першим пріоритеті
not necessary that this video will become completely
не обов'язково це відео стане повністю
public, it is possible that this video will go to the
публічним можливо це піде відео
sponsor channel, the topic may be
спонсорський канал тема можуть бути
quite specialized, but I make videos
досить спеціалізована але я знімаю Відео
on this topic first and secondly,
на цю тему в першу чергу і друге від
exclusive gifts from me for
мене ексклюзивні подарунки за
maximum support once a year and I
максимальну підтримку раз на рік і я
plan to send them to everyone this year, that is,
планую цього року всім розіслати тобто
everything will be so Subscribe, support And
все буде тому Підписуйтесь підтримайте І
when you have already subscribed and become a
коли вже ви підписались і стали
sponsor, do not forget to join this
спонсором Не забувайте додаватися в цей
our close
наш закрити